{
	"Matching": [
		{
			"Id": "1d3fb9ec-2556-487a-a648-762e1a45560a",
			"type": "Matching",
			"category": "Goland",
			"question": {
				"first question": "Some question",
				"fourth question": "Some final question",
				"second question": "Some other question",
				"third question": "Some other other question"
			},
			"choices": {
				"first choice": "Some choice",
				"fourth choice": "Some final choice",
				"second choice": "Some other choice",
				"third choice": "Some other other choice"
			},
			"answers": {
				"First answer": "Answer 1",
				"Fourth answer": "Answer 4",
				"Second answer": "Answer 2",
				"Third answer": "Answer 3"
			}
		},
		{
			"Id": "cef70071-3e20-4c1a-a2f0-bcc9352b4de2",
			"type": "Matching",
			"category": "Goland",
			"question": {
				"First question": "Some question",
				"Fourth question": "Some final question",
				"Second question": "Some other question",
				"Third question": "Some other other question"
			},
			"choices": {
				"First choice": "Some choice",
				"Fourth choice": "Some final choice",
				"Second choice": "Some other choice",
				"Third choice": "Some other other choice"
			},
			"answers": {
				"First answer": "Answer 1",
				"Fourth answer": "Answer 4",
				"Second answer": "Answer 2",
				"Third answer": "Answer 3"
			}
		}
	],
	"InfoOnly": [
		{
			"Id": "cf609cce-dffb-43cb-85a3-df40d7895648",
			"type": "InfoOnly",
			"information": "information about code"
		}
	],
	"QAndA": [
		{
			"Id": "f463ed23-5e6c-4a24-826d-96683dcef9fb",
			"type": "QAndA",
			"category": "some category",
			"question": "First question here?",
			"answer": "Answer to question."
		}
	],
	"TOrF": [
		{
			"Id": "d56a42b1-889b-46a2-a3b6-47b6e4ea4da2",
			"type": "TOrF",
			"category": "some category",
			"question": "First question here?",
			"answer": "true"
		}
	],
	"MultipleChoice": [
		{
			"Id": "89739e49-d6f5-44ca-b232-f6d1ee0d7b4d",
			"type": "MultipleChoice",
			"category": "some category",
			"question": "First question here?",
			"choices": {
				"1": "Answer to question.",
				"2": "Answer to question.",
				"3": "Answer to question.",
				"4": "Answer to question."
			},
			"answer": "1"
		},
		{
			"Id": "53510854-f1f1-4c8f-9a23-ab8751b29da3",
			"type": "MultipleChoice",
			"category": "some category",
			"question": "First question here?",
			"choices": {
				"1": "Answer to question.",
				"2": "Answer to question.",
				"3": "Answer to question.",
				"4": "Answer to question."
			},
			"answer": "1"
		}
	]
}